And, um...
(Sheldon:)I can tie a string to your leg
and fly you like a kite.
(Amy:)If you're keeping him,
I've got a cage you can borrow.
(Amy:)One of the test monkeys slipped
on a banana peel and broke his neck.
(Amy:)It was both tragic and hysterical.
Nonsense. No, Lovey Dovey
doesn't sleep in a cage.
No, Lovey Dovey sleeps
in his very own nest...
(Sheldon:)...which I'm going to get off
the window sill and put in my room.
(Sheldon:)Isn't that right, L.D.?
(Penny:)No.
(Sheldon:)Where are you going?
Come back, Lovey Dovey.
This is your home now.
(Sheldon:)I already ordered 20 pounds
of bird feed off of Amazon.
(Leonard:)- He's gone.
- I'm sorry, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)How could he do this to me?
(Sheldon:)Get back here you stupid bird
so I can Iove you!